<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>lvnt&#39;s basement</title>
    <link>https://leventbekdemir.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on lvnt&#39;s basement</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://leventbekdemir.com/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://leventbekdemir.com/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 07:47:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leventbekdemir.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Voyage to Lilliput</title>
      <link>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/a-voyage-to-lilliput/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 07:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/a-voyage-to-lilliput/</guid>
      <description>Gulliver&amp;#39;s TravelsIt would not be proper, for some reasons, to trouble the
reader with the particulars of our adventures in those seas; let it suffice to
inform him, that in our passage from thence to the East Indies, we were driven
by a violent storm to the north-west of Van Diemen&amp;#39;s Land. Twelve of our crew
were dead by immoderate labour and ill food; the rest were in a very weak
condition. On the 5th of November, which was the beginning of summer in those
parts, the weather being very hazy, t</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export: 360 Degree Semantics</title>
      <link>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/export-360-degree-semantics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 21:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/export-360-degree-semantics/</guid>
      <description>Now for the fun part: Ulysses can output your writing to a host of standard
formats, such as Plain and Rich Text, HTML, ePub, PDF and DOCX. It does so by
translating your plain text input based on the definition of the minimal markup.
If your brain starts to hurt, here’s a simple example…

Let’s assume you want to emphasize a text passage. You select the word
“emphasize” (do so), and mark it up as emphasis (tap the A| button and select
Emphasis). Notice the extra characters that were entered aro</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>deneme</title>
      <link>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/deneme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 20:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/deneme/</guid>
      <description>deneme</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iCloud and Ulysses on iPhone or Mac</title>
      <link>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/icloud-and-ulysses-on-iphone-or-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 09:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/icloud-and-ulysses-on-iphone-or-mac/</guid>
      <description>By default, your texts, along with all your groups and filters, will get stored
in iCloud. This is great, because you can seamlessly switch between iPad, iPhone
and Mac, since Ulysses works on all of them. Just visit the App Store or the Mac
App Store, install Ulysses on your devices, and you’re good to go: Outline a
short story on the subway, and work out the details at home on your Mac. So
cool.

As soon as you’re connected to the internet, sync will automatically start and
keep your library u</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start here for a quick overview of everything you need to know</title>
      <link>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 20:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#39;ve crammed the most important information to help you get started with Ghost into this one post. It&amp;#39;s your cheat-sheet to get started, and your shortcut to advanced features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customizing your brand and design settings</title>
      <link>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 20:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/design/</guid>
      <description>How to tweak a few settings in Ghost to transform your site from a generic template to a custom brand with style and personality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing and managing content in Ghost, an advanced guide</title>
      <link>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/write/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 20:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/write/</guid>
      <description>A full overview of all the features built into the Ghost editor, including powerful workflow automations to speed up your creative process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building your audience with subscriber signups</title>
      <link>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/portal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 20:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/portal/</guid>
      <description>How Ghost allows you to turn anonymous readers into an audience of active subscribers, so you know what&amp;#39;s working and what isn&amp;#39;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to grow your business around an audience</title>
      <link>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 20:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/grow/</guid>
      <description>A guide to collaborating with other staff users to publish, and some resources to help you with the next steps of growing your business</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up apps and custom integrations</title>
      <link>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/integrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 20:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leventbekdemir.com/posts/integrations/</guid>
      <description>Work with all your favorite apps and tools or create your own custom integrations using the Ghost API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://leventbekdemir.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leventbekdemir.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me  I&amp;rsquo;m a lone coder in my daily life and a software engineer in my professional life
 Development Skills go, apple, c, cplusplus, git, linux, ubuntu, visualstudio
Language Proficiency English - Professional Working Proficiency
Education  Eskisehir Osmangazi University - Electrical and Electronics Engineering (BSc) Middle East Technical University - Electrical and Electronics Engineering (MSc)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
